Abdelaziz Mahmoud

Software Engineer

Overview:

Phone: 010 2664 2884 (call or whatsapp)

Website: abdelaziz321.github.io

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/abdelaziz-mahmoud-2b344b138/

Email: abdelazizmahmoud321@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/abdelaziz321

Address: Egypt, Alexandria

I started my career in 2019-09 and worked in different places with different technologies. This small journey gave me a wide experience in many fields but I'm still trying to discover the area where I'll be proficient.

Skills:

- Strong knowledge of **PHP** with experience in **Laravel** framework.
- Strong knowledge of Python with experience in Django/Flask.
- Basic knowledge of .Net Core / EF Core / clean-architecture.
- The ability to fit into a **DevOps** culture to achieve maximum efficiency.
- familiar with cloud platforms especially Google Cloud Platform.
- Good knowledge and interest in OOP, SOLID principles, and Design Patterns.
- Strong experience in Building well-structured REST APIs.
- Good knowledge of relational databases including MariaDB/MySQL.
- Proficient in frontend technologies with experience in (VueJs / Vuex /
 NuxtJs / ChartJs /) and also familiar with Angular.

- Good knowledge of using VCS (GIT, GitHub/GitLab/BitBucket).
- Good knowledge of using Linux OS (SSH, Supervisor, Firewall, ...).
- Good communication skills and basic experience in following the Agile culture.

Work History:

VOIS "Vodafone Intelligent Solutions": Full—time 2022-02 >> now

Role: Software Developer.

Nawah.ai: Part-time remote job 2020-09 >> 2021-04

Role: Full stack Developer.

AlexApps: Full-time job 2019-09 >> 2021-09

Role: Full stack Developer

- □ building REST APIs for Mobile applications.
- Duilding Admin Panels For the managers of the mobile apps.
- ☐ Building Static Websites.

KiteAgency: Part-time remote job 2020-01 >> 2020-03

Role: Front End Developer

□ Working on the front end part of an Educational Project built with VueJs/NuxtJs

Upwork: freelancing job 2020-08 to 2020-09

Role: Full Stack Developer.

☐ Finished 1 Job with reveiw of 5 star.

Education:

College: Alexandria University - Faculty Of Science 2016 - 2022

- П *Major*: Computer Science.
- ☐ *Minor*. Statistics, studying now...

Languages:

Arabic: Mother Tongue English: Intermediate level

Other Info:

Problem solving:

- URI: urionlinejudge.com.br/judge/en/profile/169096
- ECPC Contest:
 - ECPC 2018 Qualifications Round : Twentieth Place
 - □ ECPC 2018 : One Hundred and Fifty Third Place

Tech. Interests: Networking, Security, IOT.